♪♪ [ Child Humming ]
♪♪ [ 孩子轻声哼唱 ]
♪ GEESE WALK BAREFOOT ♪
♪ 鹅儿赤脚走 ♪
♪ KRI KRA TOAD'S FOOT ♪
♪ 蟾蜍脚儿呱呱叫 ♪
I FINISHED MY BUILDING.
我的建筑完成了。
I'M FINISHED!
完成了！
THIS ONE'S BEEN WITH US FOR ONLY 36 HOURS,
这家伙才来36小时，
AND HE'S ALREADY DEMONSTRATING MORE TALENT THAN ANY OF OUR OTHERS.
就已经展现出比其他所有孩子更强的天赋。
HEY! I'M FINISHED!
嘿！ 我完成了！
HI, JAROD. I'M SYDNEY.
你好，JAROD。 我是悉尼。
I'LL BE TAKING CARE OF YOU FOR A WHILE. WHY?
接下来一段时间 由我来照顾你。 - 为什么？
WHERE'S MY MOM AND DAD?
我的爸爸妈妈在哪？
[ Man Narrating ]
[ 男声旁白 ]
MA'AM, THE MATERIALS ON BOARD ARE HIGHLY EXPLOSIVE.
女士，船上的材料 都是高危易爆品。
SO AM I.
我也是。
I NEVER AGREED WITH THE COMPANY...
我从来不同意公司...
ABOUT FLUSHING OUR TANKS AT SEA.
往海里排放废料。
I KNEW THOSE CHEMICALS HAD TO BE DOING SOMETHING NASTY.
我就知道那些化学物质 肯定在搞什么鬼。
YEAH, I'M GLAD CAPTAIN JAROD TURNED US IN.
是啊，JAROD船长举报了我们， 我很高兴。
YOU KNOW, I, UH, KINDA MISS THE GUY.
说真的，呃， 我还有点想那小子。
ALTHOUGH, UH, HE WAS A LITTLE WEIRD.
虽然，呃， 他确实有点怪。
[ Chuckles ]
[ 轻笑 ]
EVERYTHING WITH HIM WAS ALWAYS "20 QUESTIONS." AND ALWAYS THE SAME SUBJECT.
他什么事都要问个没完。 而且永远是同一个话题。
- WHICH WAS? - PEOPLE.
- 什么话题？ - 人。
THIS BELONG TO CURIOUS GEORGE?
这个是 好奇猴乔治的？
YEAH. EVERYTHING IS JUST THE WAY HE LEFT IT. COMPANY MADE SURE OF THAT.
是的。一切都 保持着他离开时的样子。公司特意这样安排的。
SAY, ARE YOU PULLIN' MY CORK ABOUT JAROD NOT REALLY BEING A CAPTAIN?
嘿，你在逗我玩吗？ JAROD真的不是 什么船长？
THANK YOU FOR YOUR HELP.
谢谢你的帮忙。
WHAT IS IT?
这是什么？
ARTICLES ABOUT THAT ALUET VILLAGE...
关于那个阿留申村庄的报道...
WHERE EVERYONE WAS GETTING SICK FROM THE CONTAMINATED FISH.
村民们因为吃了受污染的鱼 全都病倒了。
HE MUST HAVE BEEN IN QUITE A HURRY, LEAVING ALL THIS BEHIND.
他走得一定很匆忙， 才把这些都留下了。
IT'S GOT TO BE INTENTIONAL.
这一定是 故意的。
A BREAD CRUMB.
面包屑。
HE'S TRYING TO KEEP ME CLOSE.
他想让 我追着他。
YOUR LITTLE MONSTER NEEDS HIS TEDDY BEAR, HUH, SYDNEY?
你的小怪物 需要他的泰迪熊， 是吧，悉尼？
JAROD IS NOT A MONSTER.
JAROD不是怪物。
[ Giggles ] CALL HIM WHAT YOU WANT, DR. FRANKENSTEIN.
[ 咯咯笑 ] 随便你怎么叫， 弗兰肯斯坦博士。
JUST TELL ME WHERE HE IS.
告诉我他在哪。
I DON'T KNOW WHERE HE IS, MISS PARKER.
我不知道他在哪， 帕克小姐。
BUT I'M AFRAID I KNOW WHAT HE'S UP TO.
但我恐怕知道 他想干什么。
[ Woman On P.A., Indistinct ]
[ 广播中女人， 声音模糊 ]
SIR, DON'T DO THIS. LIE DOWN.
先生，别这样。 躺下。
[ Chattering ] [ Phones Ringing ]
[ 嘈杂人声 ] [ 电话铃声 ]
[ Man ] EXCUSE ME. EXCUSE ME. [ Woman Speaking Greek ]
[ 男人 ] 借过。借过。 [ 女人说着希腊语 ]
MY MOTHER'S HERE FOR HER EXPLORATORY. YOU'RE IN THE WRONG PLACE.
我妈妈是来做检查的。 你去错地方了。
YOU WANT ADMITTING. [ Continues Speaking Greek ]
你想办住院吧。 [ 继续说希腊语 ]
SPEAK ENGLISH, HONEY. SHE WON'T SPEAK ENGLISH.
说英语，亲爱的。 她不肯说英语。
SHE SAYS SHE DOESN'T WANT TO BE CUT OPEN.
她说她不想 被开刀。
SHE DOESN'T TRUST DOCTORS.
她不信任医生。
I DON'T BLAME HER.
我理解她。
[ Nurse ] END OF THE HALL.
[ 护士 ] 走廊尽头。
[ Man Shouting ] SHE SWALLOWED A MARBLE! B.P.'s 80 OVER 40.
[ 男人大喊 ] 她吞了一颗弹珠！ 血压80/40。
PULSE IS 110. RAPID AND THREADY. SHE'S CYANOTIC.
脉搏110， 又快又弱。 她发绀了。
GET DR. SHAPIRO! [ Woman ] HE'S IN O.R. 3!
快找夏皮罗医生！ [ 女人 ] 他在3号手术室！
THEN PAGE DR. TRADER!
那就呼特雷德医生！
HOLD ON, SWEETIE. YOU'LL BE FINE.
撑住，宝贝。 你会没事的。
NICOLE, GET E.N.T., STAT!
妮可， 快叫耳鼻喉科，急诊！
ALL RIGHT, FELLAS. LET'S GO. MOVE IT! ONE, TWO, THREE, GO! DR. TRADER TO O.R. 3!
好的，弟兄们，走吧。 动起来！一、二、三！ 特雷德医生到3号手术室！
- [ Paramedic ] GOT IT? - [ Nurse ] HYPEREXTEND HER HEAD.
-[ 急救人员 ] 明白了？ -[ 护士 ] 把她的头往后仰。
WHERE IS TRADER? I PAGED HIM. HE'S NOT ANSWERING!
特雷德在哪？ 我呼他了。 他没回应！
- HER PRESSURE'S FALLING. - GET ME A THREE-C.C. SYRINGE AND A SIZE EIGHT E.T. TUBE.
-她的血压在下降。 - 给我一支3毫升的注射器 和8号气管插管。
GET SECURITY TO GET THIS MAN OUT OF HERE. WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
叫保安 把这个人弄出去。 你在干什么？
- SHE'S GOING INTO RESPIRATORY ARREST. - SHE'S NOT BREATHING.
- 她要 呼吸骤停了。 - 她没呼吸了。
WOULD YOU LIKE TO DO THE TRACH? 02 SET RIGHT DOWN.
你想做 气管切开吗？ 先把氧气准备好。
- PREPARE TO VENTILATE. - NO! GET SECURITY!
- 准备辅助通气。 - 不！叫保安！
[ Nurse ] GET A DOCTOR! I AM A DOCTOR.
[ 护士 ] 快叫医生！ 我就是医生。
[ Officer ] WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
[ 警官 ] 怎么回事？
GWEN? LEAVE HIM BE.
格温？ 别管他。
GIVE ME THE SYRINGE. REMOVE THE PLUNGER.
把注射器给我。 拔掉活塞。
GIVE ME THE TOP OF THE E.T. TUBE.
把气管插管 的接头给我。
BAG.
气囊。
[ Air Expelling ]
[ 排气声 ]
- WHAT IS GOING ON HERE? - AIR ENTRY ON BOTH SIDES OF THE CHEST.
- 这里发生什么了？ - 双侧胸腔 都有空气进入。
SHE'S PINKING UP.
她的脸色在恢复。
[ Girl Inhaling, Wheezing ] NOW, THAT'S A NICE SOUND.
[ 女孩喘息、喘鸣 ] 这才是好听的声音。
[ Jarod ] WELL, I HOPE I DIDN'T CAUSE TOO MUCH CONFUSION THIS MORNING.
[ JAROD ] 希望今早没引起 太大骚动。
DON'T APOLOGIZE. YOU SAVED A LIFE.
不用道歉。 你救了一条命。
OH, DR. HENDRICKS.
哦，亨德里克斯医生。
I NEED YOUR SIGNATURE ON LINES 10 AND 14, PLEASE.
请在第10行和第14行签名。
F.Y.I., RUSSELL, IF YOU NEED ANYTHING DONE AROUND HERE, ASK GWEN.
给你个建议，拉塞尔， 如果你需要帮忙 就找格温。
I MAY RUN THIS PLACE, BUT SHE IS THE BOSS.
这地方我管， 但她才是老板。
[ Gwen ] THANK YOU. DOCTORS.
[ 格温 ] 谢谢。 医生们。
MILES! SORRY. I'M LATE.
迈尔斯！抱歉，我迟到了。
DR. JAROD RUSSELL, DR. ALAN TRADER, CHIEF OF SURGERY.
JAROD·拉塞尔医生， 艾伦·特雷德医生， 外科主任。
NICE TO MEET YOU. I HEAR I MISSED YOU IN ACTION THIS MORNING, DOCTOR.
幸会。 听说今早我错过了 您的精彩表现，医生。
NEVER SEEN A TRACH LIKE THAT. IS THAT A NEW PROCEDURE THEY'RE TEACHING AT HOPKINS?
从来没见过那样的气管切开术。 是霍普金斯教的新技术吗？
WELL, ACTUALLY, I READ IT IN A BOOK. [ Laughing ]
嗯，其实， 我在书上看到的。 [ 笑 ]
WELL, WHEREVER YOU LEARNED IT,
不管您在哪学的，
I APPRECIATE YOU STANDING IN FOR ME LIKE THAT.
感谢您 替我解围。
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED TO MY DAMN BEEPER, BUT...
不知道我的寻呼机 搞什么鬼...
IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
不会再发生了。
BRAND-NEW. EVEN TAKES MESSAGES.
全新的。 还能收短信呢。
PLEASE, SIT DOWN.
请坐。
WELL, YOUR RECORD AT HOPKINS WAS IMPECCABLE.
您霍普金斯的记录 可谓完美。
WE ARE HONORED TO HAVE YOU ON BOARD.
能邀请您加入 我们深感荣幸。
NOT MANY DOCTORS WITH YOUR CREDENTIALS COME TO A HOSPITAL AS SMALL AS OURS.
以您的资历 愿意来我们这样的小医院 可不多见。
WHY QUEEN OF ANGELS?
为什么会选天使女王医院？
WELL, I COULD TELL YOU IT WAS FOR THE CAREER OPPORTUNITY,
好吧，我可以说是因为 职业发展机会，
BUT THE TRUTH IS, YOU WERE THE ONLY HOSPITAL OFFERING STOCK OPTIONS,
但说实话， 你们是唯一一家 提供股权激励的医院，
AND RUMOR HAS IT YOU MIGHT BE PURCHASED BY AN H.M.O.
而且听说你们可能会被 某个医疗集团收购。
[ Chuckling ] WE'VE BEEN TALKING TO SOME PEOPLE.
[ 轻笑 ] 我们正在和 一些投资人谈。
- [ Laughing ] - DON'T WORRY, RUSSELL.
- [ 笑 ] - 别担心，拉塞尔。
STICK WITH US, AND YOU'LL BE DRIVING A NEW LEXUS IN NO TIME.
跟着我们干， 不出多久 你就能开上新款雷克萨斯了。
[ Both Laughing ]
[ 两人笑 ]
BUT ON TO MORE IMPORTANT BUSINESS. DO YOU PLAY RACQUETBALL?
好了， 说正事吧。 你打壁球吗？
I'VE HEARD OF IT. GOOD.
听说过。 那就好。
WE'LL HAVE A GAME.
那就好。 我们约一场。
WELL, WELCOME TO QUEEN OF ANGELS. WE ARE THRILLED TO HAVE YOU.
欢迎来到 天使女王医院。 我们很高兴有您加入。
IT'S A PLEASURE TO BE HERE.
很荣幸能来这里。
[ Miss Parker ] IMAGINE MY EXCITEMENT AT BEING RECALLED FROM CORPORATE.
[ 帕克小姐 ] 能被公司从总部召回， 我真是太激动了。
ONLY YOU...
只有你...
COULD HAVE CREATED A MESS BIG ENOUGH TO PUT ME BACK IN THE FIELD.
才能搞出这么大动静， 把我 重新派回现场。
I AM THRILLED TO BE WORKING WITH YOU AS WELL.
我也很高兴能和您 合作。
HMM. NOT FOR LONG.
嗯。 不会太久的。
WE'VE TAGGED JAROD'S ACCOUNT IN ANCHORAGE.
我们已经锁定了JAROD 在安克雷奇的账户。
HE USES AN A.T.M. ANYWHERE, AND HE'S OURS.
他只要在任何一个 自动取款机取钱， 就是我们的了。
DON'T UNDERESTIMATE HIM. IF WE'RE TO CATCH HIM, WE'LL NEED TO BE PATIENT.
别小看他。 要抓他， 我们得有耐心。
LOOK, SYD, YOU MAY BE SATISFIED IN YOUR LABORATORY,
听我说，悉尼， 你可能满足于 待在实验室里，
PROBING SMALL MINDS TO SOLVE BIG PROBLEMS.
研究小脑袋 解决大问题。
BUT I HAVE CAREER GOALS THAT DON'T INCLUDE SCHLEPPING ACROSS COUNTRY...
可我有职业目标， 不想满美国跑...
CHASING AFTER BOY WONDER.
去追那个 天才小子。
YOU WERE SUCH A HAPPY LITTLE GIRL. WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
你小时候 多开心啊。 你怎么了？
[ Beeping ] I GREW UP, SYDNEY.
[ 蜂鸣声 ] 我长大了，悉尼。
[ Buzz ] SO SHOULD YOU.
[ 门禁声 ] 你也该长大了。
THIS IS A WASTE OF ENERGY.
这是 在浪费精力。
I'VE BEEN THROUGH JAROD'S ROOM A THOUSAND TIMES.
JAROD的房间 我翻过一千遍了。
I HAVEN'T.
我没有。
WHAT ARE YOU HOPING TO FIND? HE LEFT A BREAD CRUMB ON THE TANKER.
你想找什么？ 他在油轮上留了线索。
AND I'LL BET HE LEFT ONE HERE.
我敢打赌 他在这儿也留了一个。
RUN THE SIM.
运行模拟。
THIS IS JAROD'S LAST PROJECT.
这是 JAROD最后一个项目。
WHEN THE BLACK BOX ON THIS FLIGHT WASN'T RECOVERED,
那次航班的黑匣子 没被找到，
HE SIMULATED THE FINAL MOMENTS OF THE CRASH.
他模拟了 坠机前 最后时刻的情况。
USING HIS INNATE PRETENDER SKILLS,
利用他天生的 伪装技能，
JAROD EFFECTIVELY BECAME EACH MEMBER OF THE COCKPIT CREW...
JAROD实际上 化身为驾驶舱里 每一位机组人员...
AND PINPOINTED THE CAUSE OF THE CRASH FOR OUR CLIENT.
为我们的客户 找出了坠机原因。
HMM.
嗯。
HELL OF AN ENVIRONMENT YOU KEEP HIM IN, SYD.
你把他关在 这种地方，悉尼。
AND WITH INPUT LIKE THIS, MAYBE WE'LL FIND HIM...
照这样下去， 也许我们会发现他...
MASQUERADING AS A POSTAL WORKER.
假扮成 邮递员。
HE DOESN'T MASQUERADE. HE'S A PRETENDER.
他不是假扮。 他是个伪装者。
HMM. HE BECOMES ANYTHING HE WANTS TO BE.
嗯。 他想变成什么 就能变成什么。
WELL, THE CENTRE SHOULD HAVE STUCK TO COMPUTERS FOR THEIR SIMULATIONS.
中心应该 用电脑 做模拟才对。
THEY DON'T RUN AWAY. BUT THEY'RE NOT HUMAN.
电脑不会跑掉。 但它们不是人。
THEY CAN'T TELL YOU HOW THE CREW WAS FEELING AS THE AIRCRAFT LOST POWER,
它们没法告诉你 机组人员当时 在飞机失去动力时
HOW THEIR EMOTIONS CONTRIBUTED TO THEIR FATE.
他们的情绪 如何影响了他们的命运。
JAROD CAN.
JAROD可以。
VERY, VERY CLEVER.
非常非常聪明。
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS? - AN ORIGAMI ANGEL.
- 你知道这是什么吗？ - 折纸天使。
BUT I HAVEN'T FIGURED OUT THE EMOTIONAL CONNECTION TO HIM YET.
但我还没弄明白 他和这之间的 情感联系。
IT'S NOT AN ANGEL. ITS WINGS ARE BENT. IT'S ONISIUS.
这不是天使。翅膀是弯的。是奥尼修斯。
THE GREEK GOD OF RETRIBUTION. HE DEFENDS THE WEAK AND ABUSED.
希腊的报应之神。 他保护弱者和受虐者。
I'M IMPRESSED. HOW COME YOU KNOW SO MUCH ABOUT GREEK LORE?
令人印象深刻。 你怎么对希腊神话这么了解？
OH, I DID A LOT OF FRAT BOYS IN COLLEGE.
哦，大学里 我研究过很多兄弟会男生。（美国大学兄弟会惯以希腊字母命名）
HERE'S YOUR BREAD CRUMB, SYDNEY.
这是你的线索，悉尼。
YOUR SOCIOPATH THINKS HE IS SOME KIND OF VIGILANTE...
你那反社会的小子 以为自己是 什么正义使者...
GETTING EVEN FOR THE LITTLE GUY.
要替 弱小者出头。
ST. ANDREW'S MIDDLE SCHOOL, QUEENS.
圣安德鲁中学， 皇后区。
♪♪ [ Ice Cream Truck ]
♪♪ [ 冰淇淋车音乐 ]
- IT TASTES BETTER BEFORE IT MELTS. - OH. RIGHT.
- 化了之前吃 味道更好。 - 哦。对。
THIS IS GOOD!
好吃！
THIS IS REALLY VERY GOOD!
真的非常好吃！
DO THEY WHIP AIR INTO IT TO FLUFF IT UP?
他们是不是往里打了空气 让它更蓬松？
I DON'T MAKE IT, PAL. I JUST SERVE IT.
我不做，伙计。 我只负责卖。
[ School Bell Rings ] [ Children Chattering ]
[ 学校铃声 ] [ 孩子们叽叽喳喳 ]
[ Boy ] COME ON! SHOOT IT! SHOOT IT!
[ 男孩 ] 快！ 投篮！投啊！
[ Yells ] [ Shouting, Chattering ]
[ 大喊 ] [ 叫喊、嘈杂 ]
[ Car Alarm Blaring ]
[ 汽车警报声 ]
NOW THIS IS FASCINATING. THEY WIN MONEY BY GUESSING WORD PUZZLES?
这真有意思。 他们靠猜字谜赢钱？
YOU'VE NEVER SEEN WHEEL OF FORTUNE?
你没见过 幸运之轮？
WHAT ROCK YOU BEEN LIVING UNDER?
你是从哪个石头缝里蹦出来的？
UH, I'VE BEEN BUSY.
呃，一直很忙。
"THE COURTSHIP OF MILES STANDISH."
"求爱" 迈尔斯·斯坦迪什。（朗费罗长诗《迈尔斯·斯坦迪什的求爱》主人公，此为节目猜词答案）
[ Loud Whistle ]
[ 响亮的口哨 ]
HEY!
嘿！
UH, WE GOT US A LITTLE SITUATION HERE.
呃，这里出了 小点状况。
UH, THE A.T.M. SAYS THAT YOUR BANK ACCOUNT IN ALASKA HAS BEEN FROZEN.
呃，自动取款机说 您阿拉斯加的银行账户 已经被冻结了。
NO PUN. [ Chuckling ]
没别的意思。 [ 轻笑 ]
NOW MAYBE YOU'RE HAPPY, BUT I'M OUT A BENJY FOR MY EFFORTS.
现在你高兴了， 可我跑这一趟 白干了。
DID YOU DO WHAT I ASKED?
你照我说的做了吗？
MY FRIEND, IT WAS AN OSCAR-WINNING PERFORMANCE.
老兄， 演技堪称影帝级别。
THANK YOU. YOU'RE GIVING ME A C-NOTE FOR FINDING OUT YOU'RE BROKE?
谢谢。 你给我100块 就为了查你破产了？
WE HAD AN AGREEMENT.
我们有协议的。
HEY, WHATEVER SENDS YOU.
嘿，随你怎么想。
SAY, YOU KNOW WHERE TO FIND ME IF YOU NEED ME, HUH?
需要我的时候 你知道去哪找我，嗯？
[ Knock On Door ]
[ 敲门声 ]
JUST A SECOND.
等一下。
COME IN.
进来。
GOOD MORNING, DR. RUSSELL.
早上好，拉塞尔医生。
SORRY TO BOTHER YOU, BUT COULD YOU GO TALK TO THE GREEK LADY?
抱歉打扰您， 能麻烦您去 跟那位希腊老太太谈谈吗？
SHE YELLS AT EVERYONE THAT GOES TO HER ROOM. NO ONE UNDERSTANDS WHAT SHE'S SAYING.
她对每个进她房间的人都骂， 没人 听得懂她说什么。
OKAY. I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
好的。 我这就去。
NICOLE, DO ME A FAVOR.
妮可， 帮我个忙。
HAVE THE LAB RUN A COMPLETE DIAGNOSTIC TESTING ON THIS.
让实验室 把这个血样 做个全面化验。
AND PUT A RUSH ON IT?
加急处理，好吗？
SURE. THANK YOU.
没问题。 谢谢。
[ Door Closes ]
[ 门关上 ]
[ Speaking Greek ]
[ 说希腊语 ]
YOU A DOCTOR?
你是医生？
I AM TODAY. YOU SPEAK ENGLISH.
今天是吧。 你会说英语啊。
WHEN I FEEL LIKE IT.
想学的时候才说。
AND I DON'T NEED NO OPERATION.
我不想开刀。
- HEY! - THIS HURTS, DOESN'T IT?
- 嘿！ - 疼吧？
HELL YES!
疼死了！
I HAVEN'T GONE FOR WEEKS.
我好几周没大便了。
WELL, YOU NEED TO RELAX.
你得放松点。
HOW CAN I RELAX WITH ALL THESE TESTS?
这么多检查 我怎么放松？
AND NOW THEY WANT TO CUT ME OPEN.
现在他们还要 把我开膛破肚。
OKAY. IF YOU DON'T WANT SURGERY, I'LL CANCEL IT.
好。 你不想手术， 我就给你取消。
NO SURGERY? NO.
不用手术？ 对。
I'M GONNA TRY SOMETHING ELSE.
我试试 别的办法。
YOU'RE NO DOCTOR.
你不是医生。
YOU ARE HUMAN BEING.
但你是 个好人。
MM-HMM.
嗯。
SANDY, MAKE MY DAY.
桑迪，你真行。
WELL, WE HAVE AN A.T.M. HIT ON JAROD'S ANCHORAGE ACCOUNT.
我们在JAROD 安克雷奇的账户上 截获了一次取款。
SOME GENIUS.
哪个天才干的。
SATELLITE FEED SHOULD BE UP IN... TWO SECONDS.
卫星信号 应该还有... 两秒。
HE'S IN SANTA FE, NEW MEXICO.
他在新墨西哥州， 圣菲。
CALL THE HANGAR AND GET THE JET READY.
通知机库， 准备飞机。
- HOLD IT. HE'S NOT IN SANTA FE. HE'S IN ROME. NO, LUXEMBOURG. - CHICAGO, NEW YORK.
- 等等，他不在圣菲。 他在罗马。不，卢森堡。 - 芝加哥。纽约。
THE LITTLE S.O.B. SCRAMBLED THE A.T.M. SYSTEM.
这小混蛋 把自动取款机系统 搞乱了。
MIAMI, PHILADELPHIA, BARCELONA.
迈阿密， 费城， 巴塞罗那。
HELLO, JAROD.
你好，JAROD。
[ Gwen ] YOU CANCELED MRS. NIKKOS'S SURGERY? [ Jarod ] YES, I DID.
[ 格温 ] 您取消了 尼科斯太太的手术？ [ JAROD ] 对，取消的。
FINE. YOU'RE THE DOCTOR. AS LONG AS I DON'T GET BLAMED FOR ANYTHING.
行，您是医生。 只要别让我 背黑锅就行。
AND I WOULD LIKE TO TRY HER ON AN HERB TEA CALLED CASSIA SENNA.
我想让她试试 一种叫番泻叶的 草药茶。
DOCTOR, THIS IS QUEENS. WE DON'T DO TEA.
医生，这是皇后区。 我们不玩那套。
WE DO NOW. AND I'D LIKE THE KEY TO RADIOLOGY, PLEASE.
现在开始玩了。 我想借用一下 放射科的钥匙。
WELL, ANDY'S OUT TO LUNCH, BUT--
安迪 出去吃饭了，不过——
I KNOW. THERE YOU ARE.
我知道。 找到了。
THANK YOU.
谢谢。
HI! HI, MAMA!
你好！ 你好，妈妈！
HOW YOU DOIN', LITTLE SUGAR BABY?
你好吗， 小宝贝？
GUESS WHAT IT IS.
猜猜这是什么。
[ Gwen ] I'M HOPING FOR TUNA FISH OR PEANUT BUTTER.
[ 格温 ] 我希望是金枪鱼 或花生酱。
I COULD USE A HAND WITH THESE. THAT IS, IF YOU HAVE ONE FREE.
这些我需要人帮忙拿。 如果你有空的话。
- OH, GOD. IT'S DR. RUSSELL. - [ Andy ] DR. RUSSELL?
- 天哪，是拉塞尔医生。 - [ 安迪 ] 拉塞尔医生？
I'M NEW.
我是新来的。
I'M, UH, EMBARRASSED.
我... 挺不好意思的。
BUT, UM, ALWAYS, UH-- ALWAYS HAPPY TO HELP, DOC.
不过，呃，我总是... 呃... 总是很乐意帮忙的，医生。
[ Clears Throat ]
[ 清嗓子 ]
UH, NOW--
现在——
UH, I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
呃，我不明白。
KEVIN BAILEY IS DR. TRADER'S PATIENT.
凯文·贝利 是特雷德医生的病人。
ANY SPECIAL REASON YOU'RE LOOKING AT THESE?
你有什么特别的理由 要查这些片子吗？
THAT YOU'RE IN HERE HALF NAKED?
有什么特别的理由 你在这儿 脱光了？
I CAN BE FORGETFUL IF YOU CAN.
如果你能忘， 我也能忘。
ALL RIGHT.
好吧。
YOUR PROBLEM IS RIGHT HERE...
你的问题 就在这儿...
AT THE T-EIGHTH.
T8。
THE EIGHTH THORACIC VERTEBRAE WAS CRUSHED, SEVERING HIS SPINAL CORD.
第八节胸椎 被压碎了， 脊髓断了。
KID NEVER HAD A CHANCE. THAT I UNDERSTAND. BUT LOOK HERE.
这孩子根本没机会。 这我懂。 但你看这儿。
THIS IS THE PRE-OP, AND THIS IS THE POST-OP X-RAY.
这是术前片子， 这是 术后片子。
YEAH. BUT BOTH OF THEM ARE IDENTICAL.
是啊。 但两张 完全一样。
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE? IT'S NOT.
这怎么可能？ 不可能。
SOMEONE MUST HAVE MADE A DUPLICATE OF THE POST-OP X-RAY.
一定有人 复制了 术后X光片。
YOU SEE THAT FOGGING IN THE CORNER THERE?
你看到边角那块 模糊的地方了吗？
THE OLD PROCESSOR WE KEEP IN THE BASEMENT DOES THAT.
地下室那台老洗片机 会留下这种痕迹。
I SPILLED SOME SODA ON IT WHEN I FIRST STARTED WORKING HERE.
我刚来这儿上班的时候 往上面洒过可乐。
THE NEW PROCESSOR'S FOG-FREE.
新洗片机 没这个问题。
WHY WOULD SOMEONE MAKE A COPY OF A POST-OP X-RAY AND LABEL IT PRE-OP?
为什么有人要 把术后X光片 冒充术前片？
MAKES YOU WONDER.
值得深思。
[ Young Jarod ] I'M ON THE LAST FLIGHT OF STAIRS,
[ 小时候的JAROD ] 我正走下 最后一段楼梯， （注：以下为肯尼迪遇刺案模拟训练）
TERRIFIED OF WHAT I'M ABOUT TO DO.
害怕我 即将要做的事。
MY HEART'S POUNDING. MY HANDS ARE SWEATING.
我心跳加速。 手心出汗。
I CAN HARDLY HOLD ON TO THE PACKAGE I TOLD EVERYONE WAS CURTAIN RODS.
我几乎握不住 那个包裹—— 我跟所有人说的是窗帘杆。（奥斯瓦尔德当天以此掩盖枪支）
SYDNEY, IS IT POSSIBLE FOR KIDS TO FORGET THEIR PARENTS?
悉尼，孩子有可能 忘记自己的父母吗？
[ Sydney ] KEEP YOUR MIND FOCUSED, JAROD.
[ 悉尼 ] 集中精神，JAROD。
CONCENTRATE ON THE SIMULATION.
专注于 模拟训练。
AS I NEAR THE WINDOW,
当我靠近窗户时，
I CAN HEAR THE SOUNDS OF THE CROWD RISING FROM BELOW.
我能听到 下面人群的喧嚣。
[ Young Jarod ] I CAN SEE THEM COMING.
[ 小时候的JAROD ] 我看到他们了。
HOW FAST ARE THEY GOING? FORTY MILES PER HOUR. YOU KNOW THAT.
他们开多快？ 四十英里每小时。 你知道的。
MY MOUTH'S DRY.
我嘴里发干。
MY HANDS ARE SHAKING.
我的手 在发抖。
I RAISE THE MANNLICHER CARBINE.
我举起 曼利彻卡宾枪。（Mannlicher-Carcano步枪，奥斯瓦尔德所用枪型）
I CAN'T FIRE ENOUGH SHOTS BEFORE THE CAR GOES UNDER THE OVERPASS.
在车开进 桥洞之前 我根本打不完所有子弹。
I CAN'T. I CAN'T DO THIS ALONE.
我做不到。 我不能一个人完成。
HE WASN'T ALONE.
他不是一个人。
[ Jarod ] HE HAD TO HAVE HAD HELP.
[ JAROD ] 他一定有同伙。
TRADER WASN'T ALONE EITHER, SYDNEY.
特雷德也不是一个人， 悉尼。
[ Exhales ]
[ 呼气 ]
[ Grunts, Laughs ]
[ 咕哝、笑 ]
[ Gasps ] GOOD ONE.
[ 喘气 ] 好球。
[ Exhales ]
[ 呼气 ]
GOOD GAME. [ Panting ]
好比赛。 [ 喘气 ]
DON'T LET IT BOTHER YOU. HE NEVER LETS ANYONE WIN.
别往心里去。 他从来不让人赢。
[ Jarod Laughs ] AT LEAST JAROD'S COMPETITIVE.
[ JAROD笑 ] 至少JAROD 有竞争心。
HE'S YOUNG. AND YOU'RE LAZY.
他年轻。 你太懒。
YEAH, WELL, THERE IS THAT. [ Both Laughing ]
是啊，也是。 [ 两人笑 ]
CALSIX. YOU HAVE A HEART PROBLEM?
卡尔西克斯。 你有心脏病？
MILES IS A TYPE-A TIME BOMB.
迈尔斯是 A型性格的定时炸弹。（A型性格：高度好胜、易焦虑，心脏病高发体质）
TWO HEART ATTACKS. ONE MORE, AND IT'S BYPASS TIME.
两次心脏病发作。 再来一次 就得做搭桥手术了。
WHICH IS WHY I PLAY RACQUETBALL.
所以我才打壁球。
AND I NEED A REFILL.
我需要再来一杯。
SO DO I. UM--
我也是。嗯——
IT'S MY DAY OFF.
今天我休息。
YOU EXERCISE YOUR WAY, I'LL EXERCISE MINE. [ Chuckles ]
你用你的方式锻炼， 我用我的方式锻炼。 [ 笑 ]
-SO, JAROD, DOES QUEEN OF ANGELS GET A PASSING GRADE? -ABSOLUTELY.
-JAROD，天使女王 能得几分？ -绝对满意。
FRANKLY, I EXPECTED THERE TO BE MORE FALLOUT FROM THE MALPRACTICE PROBLEMS.
说实话，我以为会 因为医疗事故问题 受到更多波及。
WELL, UNFORTUNATELY, THAT'S THE COST OF DOING BUSINESS.
很不幸， 这是 做生意的代价。
WE'VE HAD OUR DIFFICULTIES, BUT I WOULD PUT QUEEN OF ANGELS' RECORD UP AGAINST ANY HOSPITAL.
我们确实有过困难， 但我敢说天使女王医院的 记录不输给任何一家。
ARE YOU SURE THERE'S NO HIDDEN LAND MINES, EVEN WITH THE KEVIN BAILEY CASE?
你确定没有 什么隐藏隐患， 凯文·贝利案也算？
WELL, THAT WAS A TRAGEDY, BUT LET'S FACE IT--
那确实是个悲剧， 但说真的——
AN ORPHANED BOY IN A WHEELCHAIR MAKE FOR SENSATIONAL HEADLINES.
坐轮椅的孤儿 当然会成为新闻热点。
IT WAS A DAMNED WITCH HUNT.
那简直是媒体围猎。
YES. ONCE THE FRENZY DIED DOWN, THE TRUTH TOOK OVER, AND WE WERE EXONERATED.
是的。等风头过去， 真相浮出水面， 我们就被洗清了。
THAT IS ALL BEHIND US NOW.
那些都过去了。
[ School Bell Rings ]
[ 学校铃声 ]
[ Shouting, Chattering ]
[ 叫喊、嘈杂 ]
GET SERIOUS. IT'S GOOD.
认真点。 好喝的。
HASN'T ANYONE EVER TOLD YOU? YOU TALK TO STRANGERS, YOU END UP ON MILK CARTONS.
没人告诉过你？ 跟陌生人说话， 会被人贩子抓走。
MY NAME'S JAROD.
我叫JAROD。
IT TASTES BETTER BEFORE IT MELTS.
化了之前吃 味道更好。
YOUR HANDS STILL CRAMP UP WHEN YOU WHEEL?
你推轮椅的时候 手还抽筋吗？
WHAT WOULD YOU KNOW ABOUT IT?
你懂什么？
I HAVE A GOOD IMAGINATION.
我想象力丰富。
[ Kids Screaming, Shouting, Chattering ]
[ 孩子们尖叫、 叫喊、嘈杂 ]
[ Sighs ]
[ 叹气 ]
IT'S GONNA GET BETTER.
会好起来的。
[ Car Horn Honks ]
[ 汽车喇叭 ]
I PROMISE.
我保证。
[ Woman ] SIR, THERE'S A SHREVE HARMON CALLING ON LINE SEVEN.
[ 女人 ] 先生，有位什里夫·哈蒙 打七号线找您。
SHREVE AND HARMON BUILT THE EMPIRE STATE BUILDING.
什里夫和哈蒙 可是建了帝国大厦的。（悉尼借此认出JAROD：以帝国大厦设计师事务所为化名）
PUT HIM THROUGH AND TRACE THE CALL.
接进来， 同时追踪电话。
[ Buzz ]
[ 蜂鸣声 ]
[ Chuckling ]
[ 轻笑 ]
VERY CLEVER, JAROD.
真聪明，JAROD。
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
你还好吗？
I'M BROKE. YOU FROZE MY BANK ACCOUNT.
我破产了。 你冻结了我的账户。
I MUST HAVE JUST MISSED YOU IN CINCINNATI.
我一定是在辛辛那提 刚错过你。
THE FLOWERS WERE STILL FRESH.
花还新鲜着呢。
WELL, MY PARENTS HAVE BEEN DEAD FOR 30 YEARS. I FIGURED IT WAS TIME I SAID GOOD-BYE.
我爸妈已经 去世30年了。我想 是时候去告别了。
I WANT YOU TO COME HOME. [ Chuckles ]
我想让你回来。 [ 笑 ]
THERE'S AN INTERESTING WAY TO PUT IT-- "HOME."
有意思的说法——"回来"。
WHY DID YOU LEAVE? YOU'RE THE SHRINK, SYDNEY.
你为什么离开？ 你才是心理医生， 悉尼。
YOU WANT THE TRUTH?
你想要真相？
IT'S BECAUSE OF THE LIES.
是因为谎言。
YOUR LIES.
你们的谎言。
WHAT LIES?
什么谎言？
I FOUND OUT THE REAL APPLICATION OF MY SIMULATIONS, SYDNEY.
我发现了我的模拟 真正的用途，悉尼。
SOUTH PACIFIC FLEET SIMULATION 118.
南太平洋舰队 模拟118。
YOU TOOK MY RESULTS AND BLEW A SHIP OUT OF THE WATER.
你拿我的成果， 炸掉了一艘船。
A HUNDRED AND 33 PEOPLE WERE ON BOARD.
船上 有133人。
MY OUTBREAK SIMULATION?
我设计的疫情模拟呢？
YOU USED IT IN THE FIELD.
你用到现场去了。
FORTY-SIX PEOPLE DIED OF THE EBOLA VIRUS, SYDNEY.
46人死于 埃博拉病毒，悉尼。
SIMULATION 27. SIMULATION 16. SIMULATION 42.
模拟27。 模拟16。 模拟42。
JAROD, THESE WERE MILITARY CONTRACTS.
JAROD，那是 军方合同。
I HAD NO WAY OF FINDING OUT ABOUT THEIR ULTIMATE APPLICATION.
我根本没办法知道 他们最终 会怎么用。
HOW MANY PEOPLE DIED BECAUSE OF WHAT I THOUGHT UP?
有多少人是 因为我的创意而死？
YOU NEED TO COME HOME.
你该回来。
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
我很担心你。
I'VE BEEN WALKING AROUND YOUR ROOM, AND IT FEELS... EMPTY.
我一直在 你房间里走动， 感觉... 空荡荡的。
WELL, I CAN'T SAY I MISS IT.
我不能说 我想念那里。
AND BY THE WAY,
还有，
ICE CREAM IS GOOD.
冰淇淋确实好吃。
JAROD, THIS IS GETTING SERIOUS.
JAROD， 事情越来越严重了。
- THEY BROUGHT IN MISS PARKER. - UH-OH.
- 他们派帕克小姐来了。 - 不好。
WELL, YOU BETTER WATCH YOUR BACK TOO, SYDNEY.
你最好也 小心点，悉尼。
-WHAT ARE YOU DOING, JAROD? -USING THE SKILLS YOU TAUGHT ME.
- 你在做什么，JAROD？ - 用你教我的技能。
[ Man ] I'M COMPLETELY LOCKED OUT HERE. I GOT NOTHIN'.
[ 男人 ] 我完全被锁在外面了。 什么都查不到。
ARE YOU GETTING ANYTHING? NO. LET ME TRY A NEW ACCESS CODE.
你那边有收获吗？ 没有。试试 新访问码。
TALK TO ME. WE'VE BEEN LOCKED OUT.
跟我说话。 我们被锁在外面了。
OUR CLIENT HIRED US TO SEE IF THE STOCK EXCHANGE WAS VULNERABLE TO MANIPULATION.
客户雇我们 测试证券交易所 是否容易被操纵。
JAROD SPENT FOUR MONTHS ON THIS SIMULATION. WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
JAROD花四个月 做这个模拟。 问题出在哪？
THE CLIENT GAVE US FIVE MILLION TO TEST JAROD'S RESULTS.
客户给我们五百万 来验证JAROD的结果。
JAROD KNEW TODAY WAS THE DAY OF THE TEST.
JAROD知道今天 是测试的日子。
EVERYTHING WAS GOING TO PLAN UNTIL SOMEONE ON THE FLOOR STARTED TO MANIPULATE MARKETS.
一切本该按计划进行 直到交易大厅里 有人开始操纵市场。
- THEY'VE STOLEN OUR FIVE MILLION. - GEE.
-他们偷走了 我们的五百万。 - 哇。
I WONDER WHO THAT COULD BE.
我倒想知道是谁干的。
WELL, AT LEAST WE KNOW WHERE HE IS.
好吧，至少 知道他在哪了。
[ Laughing ]
[ 笑 ]
THAT'S SOME KIND MEDICINE YOU GOT THERE.
你这药真够劲。
I MIGHT LAUGH MYSELF DEAD BEFORE I POOP!
我怕笑到拉肚子 还没笑完！
[ Chuckling ] LAUGHTER IS VERY GOOD MEDICINE.
[ 轻笑 ] 笑是最好的药。
AND SO IS REFLEXOLOGY.
足底按摩也是。
NICOLE, MASSAGE THESE MARKS, WOULD YOU, PLEASE?
妮可， 帮我揉揉这几个穴位， 好吗？
THANKS.
谢谢。
YOU GONNA TELL ME THE TRUTH?
你打算 告诉我真相吗？
WHAT TRUTH?
什么真相？
A MAN WHO GIVES ME THE SUN,
一个给我阳光的人，
WHO MASSAGES MY FEET,
给我按摩脚的人，
WHO GIVES ME STINKY TEA--
给我泡难闻的茶的人——
WHO ARE YOU?
你是谁？
OH, SO MUCH SADNESS.
太多的悲伤。
AND SO MUCH JOY.
也太多的快乐。
[ Miss Parker ] COMFORTING TO KNOW THERE ARE ONLY 137 HOSPITALS...
[ 帕克小姐 ] 令人欣慰的是，大纽约地区 只有137家医院...
IN THE METROPOLITAN NEW YORK AREA.
大都市 纽约地区。
YOUR ROOMS HAVE BEEN PREPAID, MISS PARKER.
您的房间 已经预付了， 帕克小姐。
- PREPAID? - IN CASH.
- 预付？ - 现金。
AND THE GENTLEMAN LEFT THIS.
那位先生 留下了这个。
NOT A WORD.
一个字也没留。
ALAN. HEY. JAROD, HI. HI.
艾伦。嘿。 JAROD，你好。你好。
DENISE, I'LL HAVE ANOTHER GINGER ALE, PLEASE.
丹尼斯，再给我 一杯姜汁汽水， 谢谢。
MAKE THAT TWO GINGER ALES. OKAY.
来两杯 姜汁汽水。 好。
EITHER YOU'VE JUST BEEN MUGGED,
要么你刚 被人抢了，
OR IT'S BEEN ONE HELL OF A SHIFT.
要么这一班 真是够呛。
FOUR GUNSHOT WOUNDS, A LOBECTOMY AND A RUPTURED SPLEEN,
四个枪伤， 一个肺叶切除 还有一个脾脏破裂，
AND I'M ONLY HALFWAY THROUGH.
我才完成一半。
ALAN, I THINK I MIGHT HAVE SCREWED UP TODAY.
艾伦，我想我今天 可能捅娄子了。
REALLY SCREWED UP.
真的捅了大娄子。
HEY, HOW YOU DOIN'? YEAH, I'M OKAY.
嘿，你还好吗？ 嗯，我没事。
HEY, LOOK, IS THIS TRADER'S EXCHANGE?
嘿，你看， 这是特雷德的交易所吗？
GOOD. LOOK, I GOTTA GET A MESSAGE TO HIM. YEAH.
好。帮我 给他带个话。好。
SO,
所以，
WHAT'S THE TROUBLE?
什么问题？
THE LOBECTOMY? I THINK I LEFT A HEMO INSIDE WHEN I SEWED HER UP.
那个肺叶切除？ 我缝的时候 好像把血块落在里面了。
NO PROBLEM. NO PROBLEM?
没问题。 没问题？
YOU THINK THAT'S GONNA MAKE THE H.M.O. HAPPY? CHECK HER CHART.
你觉得HMO 会高兴吗？（HMO：美国健康保险机构，以严格控制医疗费用著称） 查一下她的血象。
IF THE WHITE COUNT IS SPIKED, YOU'VE FOUND YOUR HEMO.
如果白细胞数 飙升， 就说明血块还在。
WELL, THEN WHAT?
然后呢？
TAKE IT OUT.
取出来。
TELL HER YOU FOUND SOME INTERNAL BLEEDING.
告诉她你发现了 内出血。
HEY, YOU'RE THE DOCTOR. OH.
嘿，你是医生啊。 哦。
[ Pager Beeping ] AH.
[ 寻呼机响 ] 啊。
ALWAYS COUNT ON IT HAPPENING ON YOUR LUNCH BREAK, HUH?
总在吃午饭的时候响，嗯？
UM, I GOTTA GET BACK.
我得回去了。
WELL, THANK YOU FOR THE ADVICE, ALAN. YEAH.
艾伦，谢谢你的建议。 好。
[ Typing On Keyboard ]
[ 键盘敲击声 ]
[ Knock On Door ]
[ 敲门声 ]
- [ Beeps ] - COME IN.
-[ 蜂鸣声 ] -进来。
OH, GOOD. YOU'RE STILL HERE.
好。 你还在。
THE LAB REPORT ON THAT BLOOD WORKUP YOU ASKED FOR.
您要的血检 报告出来了。
- THANK YOU. - SURE.
- 谢谢。 - 不客气。
[ Door Closes ]
[ 门关上 ]
THIS ONE'S BEEN WITH US FOR ONLY 36 HOURS,
这家伙才来36小时，
AND HE'S ALREADY DEMONSTRATING MORE TALENT THAN ANY OF OUR OTHERS.
就已经展现出比其他所有孩子 更强的天赋。
HEY! I'M FINISHED!
嘿！ 我完成了！
HI, JAROD. I'M SYDNEY.
你好，JAROD。 我是悉尼。
I'LL BE TAKING CARE OF YOU FOR A WHILE. WHY?
接下来一段时间 由我来照顾你。 - 为什么？
WHERE'S MY MOM AND DAD?
我的爸爸妈妈在哪？
WHERE'S MY MOM AND DA-- [ Clicks Off ]
我爸爸妈妈在哪—— [ 切断 ]
[ Horn Blasting ]
[ 喇叭长鸣 ]
[ Man ] PLEASE EVACUATE THE BUILDING.
[ 男人 ] 请撤离大楼。
[ Alarm Blaring ] KEEP MOVING. PLEASE REMAIN CALM.
[ 警报声 ] 继续走。 请保持冷静。
THANK YOU.
谢谢。
SYDNEY. DOWNSTAIRS. PLEASE MAKE YOUR WAY TO THE EMERGENCY EXITS.
悉尼。楼下。 请走 紧急出口。
THIS WAY. [ Woman ] WAIT UP FOR ME.
这边。 [ 女人 ] 等等我。
[ Alarm Continues Blaring ] JUST ONE MINUTE, SIR.
[ 警报持续 ] 稍等一下，先生。
[ Female Voice ] PLEASE EXIT YOUR ROOM AND PROCEED TO THE NEAREST STAIRWAY EXIT.
[ 女声 ] 请 离开房间，前往 最近的楼梯出口。
MY GOD.
天哪。
SORRY TO WAKE YOU, SYDNEY,
抱歉吵醒你， 悉尼，
BUT I NEEDED TO SPEAK TO YOU FACE-TO-FACE.
但我需要 当面 和你谈谈。
YOU LOOK WELL.
你看起来不错。
WHAT'S THIS?
这是什么？
INSTRUCTIONS FOR RETRIEVING THE CENTRE'S FIVE MILLION.
追回中心 那五百万的指令。
LESS MY COMMISSION. [ Chuckles ]
扣掉我的佣金。 [ 笑 ]
DON'T LOOK SO SURPRISED. I DON'T WANT MONEY. I WANT THE TRUTH.
别那么惊讶。 我不要钱。 我要真相。
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
你在说什么？
WHO AM I? DID THE CENTRE ADOPT ME?
我是谁？ 中心是收养了我吗？
WAS I BOUGHT, OR WAS I STOLEN? AND WHERE ARE MY MOM AND DAD?
我是被买的还是被偷的？ 我的爸爸妈妈在哪？
JAROD, WE'VE BEEN OVER THIS A THOUSAND TIMES.
JAROD，这个问题 我们已经讨论过一千遍了。
YOUR PARENTS DIED IN A PLANE CRASH.
你父母死于 空难。
YES, I KNOW THE STORY, SYDNEY. IT'S BEEN BURNED INTO MY BRAIN FOR 30 YEARS.
是啊，我听过这个故事，悉尼。 30年来 它深深刻在我脑子里。
BUT, YOU SEE, I DID A LITTLE CHECKING.
但是，你看， 我查过了。
THERE'S THIS GENETIC ANOMALY THAT'S IN MY BLOOD...
我血液里有一种 基因变异...
THAT SHOULD BE IN MY SUPPOSED PARENTS.
本应该 出现在我所谓的父母身上。
BUT IT'S NOT.
但没有。
THEREFORE, IT'S IMPOSSIBLE THAT I'M THEIR SON.
所以，我不可能 是他们的儿子。
SO, THE TRUTH, FOR ONCE.
所以，这一次，说实话。
[ Man ] I THOUGHT YOU QUIT. [ Miss Parker ] SHUT UP.
[ 男人 ] 我以为你辞职了。 [ 帕克小姐 ] 闭嘴。
WHERE WERE YOU GOING, SYDNEY?
你要去哪， 悉尼？
DAMN IT! WHAT?
该死！ 什么？
NO SMOKE! OUT OF MY WAY!
着火了！ 让开！
I'M SORRY, JAROD.
对不起，JAROD。
I DIDN'T KNOW. YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME.
我不知道。 你得相信我。
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER.
但这不重要。
IT MATTERS TO ME.
这对我来说很重要。
I AM NOT GONNA BE YOUR LITTLE SCIENCE EXPERIMENT ANYMORE, SYDNEY.
我不想再做 你的科学实验了，悉尼。
I CAN BE ANYTHING I WANT TO BE. YOU TRAINED ME WELL.
我可以成为 任何我想成为的人。 你训练得很好。
I CAN BE A DOCTOR. I CAN BE AN ENGINEER. I CAN BE AN ASTRONAUT!
我可以是医生。 我可以是工程师。 我可以是宇航员！
AND SO MUCH MORE!
还有很多很多！
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHO I AM!
但我不知道我是谁！
TELL ME WHO I AM. I DON'T KNOW EITHER.
告诉我我是谁。 我也不知道。
AT THE TIME, I HAD NO REASON TO QUESTION WHAT THE CENTRE TOLD ME.
那时候， 我没有理由质疑 中心告诉我的。
I SWEAR. THEN PROVE IT.
我发誓。 那证明给我看。
GIVE ME TOMORROW'S CODE TO THE CENTRE'S MAINFRAME.
给我明天的 中心主机密码。
THE TRUTH ABOUT WHO I AM HAS TO BE IN THERE.
关于我是谁的真相 一定在里面。
YOU KNOW I CAN'T DO THAT. SYDNEY, YOU STOLE MY LIFE!
你知道我不能那么做。 悉尼， 你偷走了我的生命！
PLEASE GIVE IT BACK TO ME.
请把它还给我。
SYDNEY! SHOOT HIM!
悉尼！开枪！
7-5-1-2. GO.
7-5-1-2。走。
[ Gunshot ] [ Sydney ] NO! NO GUNS!
[ 枪声 ] [ 悉尼 ] 不行！不许开枪！
LET ME GO! [ Elevator Bell Dings ]
放开我！ [ 电梯铃响 ]
[ Grunting ]
[ 闷哼声 ]
MAKE UP YOUR MIND, SYDNEY!
做个选择吧， 悉尼！
BE A SCIENTIST OR A MOMMY!
当科学家 还是当妈咪！
YOU CAN'T BE BOTH!
你不能两个都是！
[ Man On P.A. ] YOUR ATTENTION, PLEASE. [ Train Horns Blowing ]
[ 广播 ] 请注意。 [ 火车汽笛 ]
FINAL CALL FOR ALL PASSENGERS DEPARTING ON THE ATLANTIC SPECIAL...
前往华盛顿的 大西洋特快 最后一次检票...
TO WASHINGTON, D.C....
终点站华盛顿...
WITH STOPS IN TRENTON, PHILADELPHIA AND BALTIMORE.
途经特伦顿、 费城和巴尔的摩。
NOW BOARDING ON PLATFORM 12. ALL ABOARD, PLEASE.
12号站台正在检票。 请抓紧上车。
EXCUSE ME. GWEN.
借过。 格温。
GWEN!
格温！
DR. RUSSELL. CAN I SPEAK TO YOU FOR A MINUTE?
拉塞尔医生。 我能跟您 聊两句吗？
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
有问题吗？
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO HAVE THAT.
你不应该 有这个。
I KNEW THAT TRADER WAS INVOLVED.
我就知道特雷德 脱不了干系。
WHAT I COULDN'T FIGURE OUT WAS WHY WOULD ANYBODY HELP HIM COVER IT UP?
我不明白的是 为什么有人会 帮他掩盖真相？
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
我不知道 你在说什么。
I DIDN'T EITHER, UNTIL I FOUND THIS.
我也不知道， 直到我找到了这个。
IT'S A PRINTOUT OF YOUR RECORD.
这是你档案的 打印件。
WHO ELSE KNEW YOU WERE IN PRISON BESIDES TRADER?
除了特雷德之外， 还有谁知道 你坐过牢？
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
你他妈到底是谁？
SOMEONE THAT DOESN'T THINK WHAT HAPPENED TO KEVIN BAILEY'S FAIR.
我是不认同 凯文·贝利遭遇的人。
A-AND YOU THINK I DO?
你觉得我会认同？
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT IT TOOK FOR ME TO GET BACK ON MY FEET.
你不知道我花了多大力气 才重新站起来。
I'VE GOT A JOB.
我有工作了。
I'VE GOT A GOOD MAN. I'VE GOT A BEAUTIFUL BABY BOY.
有个好男人。 有个漂亮的男娃娃。
I DON'T WANT TO LOSE THEM.
我不想失去他们。
I DON'T WANT YOU TO LOSE ANYTHING.
我不想让你 失去任何东西。
JUST TELL THE TRUTH.
说实话吧。
WHAT WOULD YOU DO IF YOUR WIFE CAME HOME AND TOLD YOU...
如果你的妻子回家告诉你...
THAT SHE'D BEEN A CRACKHEAD AND A CONVICT?
她以前是个瘾君子 还坐过牢，
I'D SAY SHE PAID HER DEBT.
我会说 她已经赎罪了。
AND I'D ASK HER WHY SHE DIDN'T TRUST ME ENOUGH TO TELL ME THE TRUTH.
我会问她为什么 不信任我 告诉我真相。
AT LEAST THAT'S WHAT I THINK I WOULD DO.
至少， 我觉得我会这么做。
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW SCARED I AM.
你不知道 我有多害怕。
I THINK I DO.
我想我能理解。
I HAD TO PAGE DR. TRADER THAT NIGHT AT THE SILVER RAIL.
那天晚上我必须在银轨酒吧 呼特雷德医生。
WE ALL KNEW HE DRANK,
我们都知道他喝酒，
BUT NOBODY WANTED TO ADMIT IT.
但没人愿意承认。
I SHOWED HIM THE X-RAYS.
我给他看了X光片。
EVEN I KNEW THAT THE BOY SHOULD HAVE BEEN STABILIZED,
连我都知道那孩子 应该先稳住病情，
BUT HE INSISTED I WAS WRONG AND--
可他非说我看错了——
HE WAS THE DOCTOR.
他是医生。
HE SEVERED THE LITTLE BOY'S SPINAL CORD WHEN HE MOVED HIM.
他移动那孩子的时候 切断了 他的脊髓。
BUT IT WAS DR. HENDRICKS WHO COVERED IT ALL UP...
但亨德里克斯医生 把所有事情都掩盖了...
AND THREATENED TO EXPOSE MY PAST IF I DIDN'T GO ALONG.
并威胁要曝光我的过去 如果我不配合的话。
SEE, UH,
你看，呃，
WHEN TRADER REALIZED WHAT HE'D DONE,
当特雷德意识到 自己做了什么之后，
HE GAVE ME THE PRE-OP X-RAYS AND TOLD ME TO BURN THEM.
他把术前X光片给了我， 让我烧掉。
BUT I COULDN'T.
但我没烧。
I WENT TO DR. HENDRICKS INSTEAD.
我去找了 亨德里克斯医生。
I DON'T KNOW WHY I THOUGHT IT WOULD DO ANY GOOD.
我不知道我为什么会觉得 那样做会有用。
HE'S BEEN COVERING FOR TRADER FOR YEARS.
他替特雷德 遮掩好多年了。
HE TOOK THE X-RAYS,
他拿走X光片，
AND HE MADE ME SWEAR THAT I WOULDN'T TELL ANYBODY THAT HE HAD 'EM.
让我发誓 不告诉任何人 他保管着这些。
HE SAID THAT HE MIGHT BE ABLE TO USE THEM FOR INSURANCE.
他说也许可以用这些 来处理保险的事。
[ Sighs ]
[ 叹气 ]
THANK YOU.
谢谢你。
DR. HENDRICKS ISN'T GONNA GIVE YOU THAT FILM.
亨德里克斯医生 不会给你那些片子的。
HE'D RATHER DIE THAN RISK THAT HOSPITAL SALE.
他宁可死 也不愿冒医院交易泡汤的风险。
DR. TRADER. ALAN? IT'S JAROD.
特雷德医生。 艾伦？ 我是JAROD。
WE NEED TO TALK. ABOUT WHAT?
我们需要谈谈。 谈什么？
UH, NOT ON THE PHONE.
呃，电话里不好说。
CAN YOU MEET ME TODAY AT THE SILVER RAIL AT NOON?
今天中午能见一面吗？ 银轨酒吧？
I'LL BE THERE. THANKS, ALAN.
我会到的。 谢谢，艾伦。
[ Punching Keypad ]
[ 按键盘 ]
MILES. JAROD RUSSELL.
迈尔斯。 JAROD·拉塞尔。
JAROD. WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
JAROD。 我能帮什么忙？
HOW ABOUT ANOTHER GAME OF RACQUETBALL?
再来一局 壁球？
WHY WOULD YOU WANT ANOTHER GAME SO SOON AFTER I CRUSHED YOU?
刚把我打得落花流水 你就想再来？
[ Chuckles ] TO RETURN THE FAVOR. HOW ABOUT TODAY AT NOON?
[ 笑 ] 礼尚往来。 今天中午怎么样？
WELL, IT'S YOUR FUNERAL.
好吧， 随你。
WELL, WE ALL HAVE TO GO SOMETIME.
人总有一死。
[ Groans ] POINT, GAME, MATCH.
[ 呻吟 ] 一比零，我赢了。
TOSS ME MY WATER, WILL YA?
把水扔给我，行吗？
SURE, MILES.
好，迈尔斯。
[ Hendricks Grunting ]
[ 亨德里克斯喘气 ]
GEEZ. [ Sighs ]
天。 [ 叹气 ]
SO, JAROD, WHY THE SELF-TORTURE?
JAROD， 干嘛这么自虐？
WELL, I FIGURE I LET YOU WIN A FEW GAMES,
我想着 让你赢几局，
I EARN YOUR PITY, YOU CUT ME A BETTER STOCK OPTION.
赢得你的同情， 你给我更好的股权。
WELL, MY PITY DOESN'T COME CHEAP.
我的同情 可不便宜。
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING-- YOU RAN ME ALL OVER THAT COURT. YOU ARE GETTING BETTER.
我跟你说—— 你在球场上把我遛得够呛。 你进步挺快的。
I'VE BEEN PRACTICING. AH.
一直在练习。 啊。
BUT I WON.
但我赢了。
[ Gasping, Panting ]
[ 喘气 ]
YOU OKAY, MILES?
你还好吧，迈尔斯？
JAROD--
JAROD——
[ Gasping ]
[ 喘气 ]
MILES?
迈尔斯？
CAN SOMEBODY CALL AN AMBULANCE?
谁能叫一下救护车？
DR. RUSSELL SAYS HE'S RUNNING A BIT LATE.
拉塞尔医生说 他可能要晚点到。
SHOW ME A DOCTOR WHO ISN'T, HUH?
找哪个医生 不迟到，嗯？
I'LL HAVE ANOTHER QUICK ONE.
我再 来一杯。
SURE.
好。
GET O.R. 3 SET. DR. HENDRICKS IS HAVING A HEART ATTACK.
准备3号手术室。 亨德里克斯医生 心脏病发作。
[ Woman ] WATCH YOUR BACK!
[ 女人 ] 小心后面！
PULSE IS 112 AND THREADY. B.P. HAS DROPPED FROM 75 TO 60.
脉搏112，又细又快。 血压从75掉到60。
I WANT YOU TO START HIM ON A NITRO DRIP AND GET HIM PREPPED FOR SURGERY, STAT!
上硝酸甘油点滴， 准备急诊手术！
YOU LIED TO ME.
你骗了我。
LAST NIGHT, YOU TOLD ME JAROD CAME HERE TO RETURN THE FIVE MILLION.
昨晚你告诉我 JAROD来这里 是归还那五百万。
ALL HE REALLY WANTED WAS THE MAINFRAME CODE. IT WAS THE LEAST I COULD DO.
他真正想要的 是主机密码。 这是我唯一能做的。
HE WAS LIED TO ABOUT HIS PARENTS. SO WAS I.
他的身世被骗了。 我也是。
STOP POUTING.
别撅嘴了。
IT WAS NEED-TO-KNOW. YOU DIDN'T.
那是"需要知道"。 你不需要知道。
ANYWAY, YOU'VE DONE US ALL A GREAT FAVOR. YOU SEE, I TAGGED JAROD'S FILE.
反正，你帮了我们大忙。 你瞧，我给JAROD的档案加了追踪。
HE LOGGED ON THIS MORNING. WHERE IS HE?
他今早登录了。 他在哪？
QUEEN OF ANGELS HOSPITAL. THEY'RE BRINGING THE CAR AROUND NOW. LET'S GO.
天使女王医院。 他们正在备车。 走吧。
THE CENTRE WANTS HIM ALIVE.
中心要他活着。
PREFERABLY.
最好活着。
[ Monitor Beeping ]
[ 监护仪响 ]
MILES, WE WERE UNABLE TO BRING IN A CARDIOLOGIST FAST ENOUGH.
迈尔斯，我们来不及 请心脏专科医生了。
BUT DON'T WORRY. I PAGED DR. TRADER.
但别担心。 我呼了特雷德医生。
NO--
不——
HE'LL TAKE CARE OF YOU, MILES.
他会照顾好你，迈尔斯。
- HE TOOK CARE OF KEVIN BAILEY. - NO.
- 他"照顾"过凯文·贝利。 - 不。
[ Gasping ] PLEASE.
[ 喘气 ] 求你了。
YOU DO THE OPERATING.
你来主刀。
OKAY, OKAY-- O-OKAY, MILES. NO PROBLEM.
好、好—— 好，迈尔斯。没问题。
BUT FIRST,
但首先，
YOU TELL ME WHERE KEVIN BAILEY'S PRE-OP X-RAYS ARE.
你告诉我 凯文·贝利的术前X光片 在哪。
[ Continues Gasping ]
[ 继续喘气 ]
BEHIND THE PUNJAB PAINTING IN MY OFFICE.
我办公室那幅旁遮普画 后面。
NOW, YOU DO THE OPERATION, JAROD.
现在，你来 做手术，JAROD。
I-I-I'D LIKE TO, MILES. I REALLY WOULD.
我——我——我想做，迈尔斯。 真的想。
BUT THAT WOULDN'T BE ETHICAL.
但那样做 不符合职业道德。
YOU SEE,
你知道的，
I'M NOT REALLY A DOCTOR.
我并不是真正的医生。
AND YOU'RE NOT REALLY HAVING A HEART ATTACK.
你也并不是真正 在犯心脏病。
TRADER, HE'S ALL YOURS.
特雷德，他是你的了。
OKAY.
好吧。
LET'S DO THIS.
开始吧。
[ Wheezing ] JAROD. JAROD--
[ 喘息 ] JAROD。JAROD——
[ Miss Parker ] WE'LL START ON THE FIRST FLOOR AND WORK OUR WAY UP.
[ 帕克小姐 ] 我们从一楼开始 往上找。
JAROD DOES NOT LEAVE.
JAROD休想离开。
NICOLE?
妮可？
WOULD YOU PAGE SECURITY AND HAVE THEM STOP DR. TRADER FROM OPERATING?
能呼一下保安吗？ 让他们阻止 特雷德医生做手术？
HE'S DRUNK. OH, MY GOD!
他喝醉了。 天哪！
YEAH.
是啊。
YOU TAKE THAT SIDE.
你去那边。
JAROD!
JAROD！
GUESS WHAT. GUESS WHAT I DID TODAY!
猜猜看。 猜猜我今天做了什么！
OH! WELL, THAT'S GREAT!
哦！ 太棒了！
SORRY.
抱歉。
HE'S GOT TO BE IN ONE OF THESE ROOMS.
他肯定在 某个病房里。
[ Mrs. Nikkos Screams ]
[ 尼科斯太太尖叫 ]
LET'S GO!
走！
HEY! A MAN! HE RAN OUT THE FIRE ESCAPE!
嘿！有个人！ 他从 消防通道跑了！
HE'S HEADING TO THE ROOF!
他往天台去了！
[ Speaks Greek ] [ Mrs. Nikkos Laughs ]
[ 说希腊语 ] [ 尼科斯太太笑 ]
JAROD!
JAROD！
[ Woman On P.A. ] YOUR ATTENTION, PLEASE.
[ 广播 ] 请注意。
FLIGHT 1428 TO SAN DIEGO WILL BE DEPARTING FROM GATE 12.
飞往圣地亚哥的1428航班 将从12号登机口起飞。
PLEASE HAVE YOUR BOARDING PASSES READY.
请准备好 您的登机牌。
YOU'D BETTER BOARD, SIR. YOU DON'T WANNA MISS THE FLIGHT.
先生，您该登机了。 不想误机吧。
DON'T WORRY.
别担心。
THEY'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE WITHOUT ME.
他们没有我 哪儿也去不了。
[ Mews ]
[ 猫叫声 ]